Guide to the New York State Board of Mediation Cases 1952-1964
New York State Board of Mediation Cases
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
New York State Board of Mediation Cases, 1952-1964
5581
New York State Board of Mediation
115 linear ft.
Records (documents).
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Records of specific mediation cases from the New York State Board of Mediation.
SUBJECTS
Names:
New York (State). Board of Mediation.
Subjects:
Mediation and conciliation, Industrial--New York (State); Arbitration, Industrial--New York (State)
Form and Genre Terms:
Records (documents)
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
CONTAINER LIST
- A 1 - A 11, A 100 - A 189 (1938). (Box 1)
  - SAML Gordon, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Ranch Meat Markets, Inc. Harry Olstein, Pres., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Wearbest Slipper Company, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Manhattan Stationery, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Scrap Iron and Steel Institute, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Michael, Raymond S. trading as Savoy Shops, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - M & M Kiddie Shop, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Eugene Modell Radio and Tel. Co., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 1027 Westchester Avenue Corp., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Mrs. Goodman, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - La Valle, Inc., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Strauss Fasteners, Inc., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - New York Furniture Merchants Assn., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - All Brands Tire Exchange, Inc., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Oriental Paper Box Mfg., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Pinaud Incorporated, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Fybro Refrigerator Corp., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - La Salle Watch Company, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Orzechowski Provision Company, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Ramsey Shoe Company, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Principal Shoe Company, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Jerome Specialty Shop, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Loramine Drug, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Royal Office and Supply, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Standard Body Corporation, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Meyer's Stationery, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Two Ninety-Nine Broadway, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Silver Rod Stores Co., Inc., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Lane Jewelry, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - J. Rabinovich, Inc. and Solesto, Inc., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Goodseit and Sonnenschein doing business under "Levine Bros", 1938 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Schwartz Bros. Mill Enterprise, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - California Grape Products Co. Ltd., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Suffolk County Truck Owners Assn., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Long Island Mattress Company, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - H.H. Waters Jewelry Company, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Meat Dealers, Ye Old New York Branch of N.Y. State Assn. of Retail (S. Mansbach), 1938 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Kartineger and Niedenberg, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Riveria Pharmacy. Jay-Arr Drug Co., Inc., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Wholesale Fresh Water Fish Merchants, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Knickerbocker Stationery, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - A. Werman Shoe Company, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Kraft Associated Distributors, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Capitol Paint & Varnish Works, Inc., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Studio Apartments, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Richard Schnibbe, Inc., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Ludwig Baumann, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Tiara Products Co., Inc., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - New York Furniture Merchants Assn., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - New England Curtain Shop, Inc., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Morris Abrams, Inc., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Progressive Furniture Company, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Jacob Schoenfeld, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Merribee Art Embroidery Co., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Glaser Bros., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Oxenberg Bros., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Vermite Exterminating Co., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - United States Lines Company, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Strike of Misc. Labor, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Reliable Furniture Company, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Madow's, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Champion Shoe Manufacturing Corp., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Consolidated Tinware Co., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Mace Company (Textile Workers Org. Committee), 1938 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - I. Gralla, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - B. Cribari & Sons, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Siegel's Drug Store, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - P.B. Baking Co., H and H Baking Co., Princeton Baking Co., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Hoover Sales Company, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Daniel Jones, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Goldman Bros., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - William Goldblum & Co., Inc., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Astor Shoe Company, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Hara, Irving, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Firor, Frank M., Inc., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Gottbetter Brothers, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Rothberg and Katz, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Swan Laundry, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Roman Macaroni Co., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - A.T. Concord & Bros., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Coyne & Delaney Corporation, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Stevens, Walter B. and Son, Inc., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - United States Cloth Cutting Machine Co., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Smoked Fish Industries (Employers), 1938 (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Weil and Company, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Louis Seiler Furniture Co., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - L. Somomon & Son, Inc., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Benay Art Embroidery Company, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - David Karron, Inc., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - Malina Company, Inc. and Bendythe Co., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Undergarment and Negligee Workers, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Seeman Bros., Inc., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - Automotive Specialty Corp., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - Bellows & Co., Inc., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - E.J. Barry Co., Inc., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - Lacidem Realty Corporation, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 96)
  - Hills Brothers, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 97)
  - Komfort Mattress, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 98)
  - Glove Manufacturers Arbitration, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 99)
  - David Bogen Co., Inc., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 100)
  - 1938 (Box 1, Folder 101)
  - Monastersky Rubin, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 102)
  - Savoy Decorators, Inc., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 103)
  - H. Fleisig, Inc., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 104)
  - United-Cigar Whelan Stores Corp., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 105)
  - Garrett & Co., Inc., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 106)
  - Ormont Machine Co., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 107)
  - B. Kittay and Sons, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 108)
  - Sunshine Radio System, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 109)
- A 190 - A 368 (1938- ). (Box 2)
  - Monastersky, Rubin, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Savoy Decorators, Inc., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - H. Fleisig, Inc., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - United-Cigar Whelan Stores Corp., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Garrett & Co., Inc., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Ormont Machine Co., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - B. Kittay and Sons, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Sunshine Radio System, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Square Music and Sport Shop, Inc., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Gotbetter Brothers, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Handy and Specialty Co., Inc., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Modern Refrigerator Corp., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Goldman, Benjamin, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Jerome Hosiery and Underwear Inc., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Non-Sectarian Anti-Nazi League, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Super Metal Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Wirklich, Joseph (Estate of), 1938 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Royal Office Supply Corp., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - William Weinberg Company, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Rockwell's Bakery, Inc., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Sky Chief Radio Corporation, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Roberts Radio Company, Inc., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Stoller, Dora (Estate of), 1938 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Globe-Brenner Corporation, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - F.A. Schurmann, Inc., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Superior Dairy Products, Inc., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Goldberg, N., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Grandview Dairies, Inc., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Scall Undergarment Company, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Stablemen and Helpers of America, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Aaron Streit, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Olympia Baking Company, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Smartwear Slipper Company, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Princely Products, Inc., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Radin Fish Co., Inc., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Venice Curtain Stores Corp., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Steinhardt Company, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Kumfort Mattress Co., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Horowitz Bros. and Margareten, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Municipal Shoe Company, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Eveready Hardware Mfg. Co., Inc., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Michael Vitolo, Inc., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - (Blum, Frank, Fishkin) Ye Olde N.Y. Branch, N.Y. State Assn. of Retail Meat Dealers, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - S. Beckenstein, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Mutual Sewing Machine Dealers, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Krasnoff Dental Laboratories, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Pioneer Watch Case Company, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Mayer and Herman Shoe Company, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Kesselman's Department Store, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Manhattan Pharmacy, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Bristol Pharmacy, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Dubrow Pure Food Co., Inc., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - New York and Brooklyn Casket Company, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - S. and W. Fine Foods, Inc., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Marcus Box Spring Company, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - New York Federation of Food Merchants, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Non-Sectarian Anti-Nazi League, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - S. and B. Stores, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Service Headquarters Inc., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Principal Shoe Company, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - WM. A. Taylor and Co., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Transformer Corporation of America, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Mayer Harman Shoe Company, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Fur Machine Dealers Association, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Levinson Photo Service, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Sclafani Import Co., Inc., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Yelloway Transportation Co., Inc., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Paramount Silk House, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Samuel Klein and Sons`, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Principal Shoe Company, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Eveready Hardware Mfg. Co., Inc., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Wholesale Tobacco Distributors of New York, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Rosola Food Products, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Ormont Machine Co. Inc., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Accurate Shoe Company, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Lane Jewelry Co., Inc., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Progress Shoe Company, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Block Drug Stores Inc., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Broadway Central Hotel, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Rayburn Cafeteria Inc., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - T. Freedman, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - La Valle Shoe Inc., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Weil Furniture Company, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Hara, James, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Wolf Paper Box Company, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Lion binding and Trimming Company, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Hotel St. George, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Kaplan, Philip, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Janus Operating Co., Inc. (Golden Crest Holding Corp.), 1938 (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - Anker's Decorators, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - Reliable Furniture Company, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - Pincus Curtain Store, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - Stahl Meyer Co., Inc., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - 1005 Jerome Avenue (Fee Equities Inc.), 1938 (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - Saporta, O., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 95)
- A 370 - A 507 (1938). (Box 3)
  - William Weinberger (N.Y. State Assn. of Retail Meat Dealers, Inc.), 1938 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - National Hardware Co., Inc., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Broadway Window Cleaning Co., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Queens borough Farm Products Inc., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Municipal Dairy, Inc., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - J. Pressman and Co., Inc., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Display Well Inc., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - National Shoe Company, Inc., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Cooper Stamp Works, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Union Cutlery Co., Inc., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Six Seventy Seven, Local and Eleven Eighty Five, Local, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Triangle Bus Corp., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Bronx Retail Meat Dealers Assn., Inc., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Englander Bed Spring Co., Inc., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Plaza Auto Body Corporation, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Riviera Pharmacy, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Pinaud, Inc., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Dobrin Supply Co., Inc., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Cornelia Footwear, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Schlesinger Bros., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Canada Dry Ginger Ale, Incorporated, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Goldman's Yarn Store, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Weylin Pharmacy, Inc., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Schwartz, Samuel S., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Putterman Footwear Corporation, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Madow's, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Jones, William C., Envelope Co., Inc., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Lewis, David, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Pilgrim Pharmacy, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Midtown Hotel operating Cadillac Hotel, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Louis Cohen and Son, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - George Schaefer and Sons, Inc., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - W.E. Pruden Company, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Bayside and Quick Delivery Co., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Canada Dry Ginger Ale Inc., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Nathan Baer Candy Company, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Mount Vernon Die Casting Corporation, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Barry Pharmacy, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - John Casale, Inc., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Traders Trucking Corporation, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Mauro, Michael, Member, Bronx Wash. Hts. Br. Retail Meat Dealers, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Royal Butchers, member, Bronx and Wash. Hts. Br. Retail Meat Dealers, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - 208 West 148th St. Realty Corp., 259 West 143rd Street, Inc., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Dumont Electric Company, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Bias Fabric Manufacturers. Assn., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Municipal Shoe Co. Inc., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Sheffield Farms Co., Inc., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Philson Manufacturing Company, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Edway Meat Market, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Warner Furniture Co., Inc., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Cleaners and Dyers BD of Trade Inc., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Freedman's (Tillie Freedman), 1938 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Five Star Shoe Company Inc., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Arnold Constable and Company, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Peller and Silverman, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Bellecraft Slipper Company, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Greenwood Cemetery Association, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - United Cigar Whelan Stores Corporation, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Thompson Co., John R., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Dictograph Products Co., Inc., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - J.H. Semel and Company, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Fourteenth Street Store, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Master Dy Cleaning Chain Store Operators Inc., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - La Valle Inc., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Astor Shoe Company, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - La Salle Slipper Company, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - National Hardware Company, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - American Beverage, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Cohn and Rosenberger Inc., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Davega City Radio, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Rose, Frank and Adler, Sam, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Maxwell, Jack, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Werman's, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Wearbest Slipper Company, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Bluestone Photoprint Company, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Benenson Realty Corporation (1018 E. 163rd Street), 1938 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Dorsen Wolf Drug Corporation, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Intner, William Co., Inc., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Purepac Corporation, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Truitt Shoe Company, Inc., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Consolidated Tinware Co., Inc., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - Savoy Specialty Shop, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - Schenley Import Company, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - Hercules Shoe Corporation, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - Hayden Drug Shop, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - Belfert Furniture Company, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - Henry Romeike Inc., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 87)
  - Westchester Service Corporation, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - Weiner Bros., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - Non-Sectarian Anti Nazi League, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - Sam Ader, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 91)
  - Eugene Modell Radio and Television Co., Inc., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - Wearbest Slipper Company, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - Micamold Radio Corporation, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - Coal Merchants Association Inc., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 95)
  - Jacob, H. and Sons, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - Garden Pharmacy, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 97)
  - Modell Radio Company, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 98)
  - Landau, Henry, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 99)
  - Piser and Company, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 100)
  - Monastersky, Rubin, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 101)
  - F. and R. Mattress Company, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 102)
  - Boro Paper Box Company, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 103)
- A 507 - A 713 (1939). (Box 4)
  - Loft, Inc., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Progress Shoe Company, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Bookstaver, B.S. Dr., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - European Radio Company, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Abbey Photo Corporation, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Paragon Slipper Company, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - United Cigar Whelan Stores Corp., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Riggs Restaurant, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - L. and B. Hosiery, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - United Cigar Whelan Stores Corp., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Earlswood Court Realty Corporation - Premises 351 St. Nicholas Ave., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Intner Company, William Inc., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Brooklyn Table Company, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Jones Company, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Katz, M. and Co., Inc., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Well Made Parlor Frame Co., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Koestler Bros. Inc., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Warner Furniture Company, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Mendel Drug Store, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - W.H. Joseph and Son, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Lanner Bros., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Graham Motors, Inc., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Art Steel Company Inc., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Goldman's Yarns, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Original Dave's, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Association of Bedding Manufacturers, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Kumfort Bedding Manufacturer Company, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Julius Altschul Inc., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Eighteen Fiftyone Seventh Avenue Holding (1851 Seventh Ave. Holding Corp.), 1939 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Radio Tube Trading Co., Inc., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Luria, M.S., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Dempsey, WM. S. Realty Co. (Controlling 574 St. Nicholas Ave.), 1939 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Cooper Radio and Sport Shop, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Micamold Corp., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - May Knitting Co., Inc., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Le Winter Radio Co., Inc., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Champion Shoe Co., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Mayer Herman Shoe Co., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Principle Shoe Corp., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Kumfort Bedding, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Long Island Macaroni Company, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Lebensfeld Brothers, Inc., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Standard Flashlight Company, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Bond Brothers, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Nancy Lee Millinery, Inc., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - John R. Thompson Co., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Diamond Candle Company, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - J.B. Slattery and Bro., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Gottfried Baking Co., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Fairchild Aerial Camera Corp., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Embassy Pharmacy, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Associated Plastering Co., Inc., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Blacharsky, S., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Wachtel, J. Biscuit Company, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Levenson, Jack, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Edgar Guifrida Millinery, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Bernheimer Co., G.A., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Lesell Pharmacy, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Jeannette's Millinery, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Indelacato, Joe, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Fay's Millinery, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Beyda and Co., Inc., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Grobifker, Nathan c/o Kanter's Department Store, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Associated Marble Manufacturers Inc., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Weiser's Ladies Shop, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Weiss Bros., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Deitz, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Restaurant Guild Inc., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Kaufman Pharmacy, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Excellent Housekeeping Co., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Sol Broome and Co. Inc., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Wearbest Slipper Company, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Automatic Woven Wire Co., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Daly Millinery Inc., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Rubenstein's Beigel Bakery, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Greater New York Glazers Assn. Inc., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - Formfitting Slipper Corporation, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - Decca Records, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - Stolpen Cigar Corporation, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - Famous Dairy Cafeteria, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - Max Nadell, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - Paper Box Credit Bureau, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - Abraham Gerstenzang, Inc., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - United Parcel Service, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Audak Company, Inc., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - I.B. Kleinert Rubber Co., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Wreckers and Excavators Inc., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - G.N.O. Drug Co., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - United Cigar Whelen Stores Corp., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 89)
  - Lee Mart Cigar and Candy Co., Inc., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 90)
  - Berry Bedding Company, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - Superior Drug Service`, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 92)
  - Buckingham Pharmacy Inc., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 93)
  - Janpolis, Max, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 94)
  - Fishkin, Julius, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 95)
  - Cohen, Benjamin, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 96)
  - Manoil Manufacturing Co., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 97)
  - Merit Kingston Cheese Co., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 98)
  - Spanier, Aaron, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 99)
  - F.H.S. Cigar Stores, Inc., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 100)
  - Spear and Company, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 101)
  - Madow's Jewelry Co., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 102)
  - Gotbetter Brothers, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 103)
  - Friedman's Sport Shop Philip Sulitan, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 104)
  - L. Borg, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 105)
  - Mercantile Drug, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 106)
  - Elite Specialty Metal Company`, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 107)
  - Royal Meat Market, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 108)
  - Samuel Meyers, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 109)
  - Lazar's Department Store, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 110)
  - Hartnagel, Otto, Inc., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 111)
  - Silver Standard, Inc., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 112)
  - Empire Photographers, Inc., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 113)